Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Papers AIA.031.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Photographs, circa 1930-2002; 8 boxes
  - Subseries A: Slides, 2011
    - World's Fair of 1982 (Knoxville, Tennessee): Slideshow- People Around Here (Folder 2) (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - World's Fair of 1982 (Knoxville, Tennessee): Slideshow Alternates (Folder 1) (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - World's Fair of 1982 (Knoxville, Tennessee): Slideshow Alternates (Folder 2) (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - World's Fair of 1982 (Knoxville, Tennessee): Slideshow Alternates (Folder 3) (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Subseries B: Prints
    - All-Ireland Orchestra feat. Jimmy McDade (Phila, PA), 1940s-1950s (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - AOH - Highbridge All-Accordion Band (Bronx, NY), 1955 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Augusta Heritage Center (Elkins, W. Va.), 1992 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - "Augusta Week 2" (panoramic group photograph), 1992 (Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file 2)
    - Augusta Heritage Center (Elkins, W. Va.), Jul, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Augusta Heritage Center (Elkins, W. Va.), undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Augusta Heritage Center (Elkins, W. Va.), undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Augusta Heritage Center (Elkins, W. Va.): 20th Anniversary Poster One, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Augusta Heritage Center (Elkins, W. Va.): 20th Anniversary Poster two, 2022 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Augusta Heritage Center (Elkins, W. Va.): 20th Anniversary Poster Three, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Augusta Heritage Center (Elkins, W. Va.): 20th Anniversary Poster Four, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Augusta Heritage Center (Elkins, W. Va.): 20th Anniversary Poster Five, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Blake, Nancy and Norman, undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Blended Scotch, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Bothy Band, 1970s (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Briley, Rosalyn, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Britton, Timmy and Ben Ruthe, 1970s (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Brown, Patsy, c.1945 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Burke, Joe (accordion), 1980s (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Burke, Kevin, 1970s (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Byrne, Tom and Tom McCaffrey, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 2, Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Cahill, Eddie, undated (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Cahill, Eddie, undated (Box 31, Folder 22, Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Carroll, Liz, undated (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Carroll, Liz, undated (Box 31, Folder 24, Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Carton, Mickey, Mary Carton and Ruthie Morrissey, 1950s, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Carton, Mickey, Mary Carton and Ruthie Morrissey, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 5, Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Catskills Festival (Leeds, NY), 1978 (Box 31, Folder 27, Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Caulfield, Thomas, undated (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Cherish the Ladies, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Cherish the Ladies, undated (Box 34, Folder 8, Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Chicago Ethnic Arts Project, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Chicago Musicians: Keanes, Shannon, Cooley, undated (Box 31, Folder 32, Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Chicago Musicians: Rice, etc., undated (Box 34, Folder 10, Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Chieftains, undated (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Clancy Brothers and Tommy Makem, undated (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Clark, Dennis (family photos), undated (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Clancy, Willie, undated (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Coen, Fr. Charlie, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 12, Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Coen, Fr. Charlie, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Coen, Fr. Charlie, undated (Box 34, Folder 13, Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Coen, Jack, undated (Box 34, Folder 14, Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Comhaltas on Tour (Chicago, IL): Shannon, McGlynn, Coens, Henry, Flatley, late 1970s (Box 34, Folder 15, Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Comhaltas on Tour (Chicago, IL): Shannon, McGlynn, Coens, Henry, Flatley, late 1970s (Box 34, Folder 16, Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Comhaltas on Tour (Chicago, IL): Shannon, McGlynn, Coens, Henry, Flatley, late 1970s (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Collecting, undated (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - Comhaltas Convention, undated (Box 34, Folder 17, Box 31, Folder 46)
    - Conlon, P.J., undated (Box 31, Folder 47)
    - Concert for Joe Doherty: Symphony Space (New York, NY), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 48, Box 34, Folder 19, Folder 18)
    - Connolly, Seamus, 1990s (Box 31, Folder 49)
    - Contact Sheets: Multiple Artists: A. O'Brien, Reavy, Cahill, DeDanaan, G. Kelly, Rafferty, Coens, undated (Box 31, Folder 50)
    - Cooley, Joe and Kevin Keegan (Oversized), undated (Box Shared Tamiment 065, Folder 10)
    - Crehan, Junior, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 51)
    - Crowley, Jimmy, undated (Box 31, Folder 52)
    - Cruise, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 53)
    - Cruise, Mar, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 54)
    - Cruise: Virgin Islands, undated (Box 31, Folder 55, Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Cruise: Virgin Islands, undated (Box 31, Folder 56, Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Dancers, 1950s-1990s (Box 31, Folder 57)
    - DeDanaan, 1970s (Box 31, Folder 58)
    - DeMarco, Tony and Brian Conway, 1970s (Box 31, Folder 59)
    - Denman, Todd and Bill Dennehy, undated (Box 31, Folder 60)
    - Dervish, undated (Box 31, Folder 61)
    - DeValera, Eamon, 1948 (Box 31, Folder 62)
    - Doherty, Tom, undated (Box 31, Folder 63)
    - Donegal Society Golden Jubilee Banquet (Phila, PA) (Oversized), May 11, 1938 (Box Shared Tamiment 149, Folder 6)
    - Duplicates for Exhibits, undated (Box 35)
    - Egan, Seamus, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 64)
    - Emerald Isle Orchestra feat. Will Regan (Phila, PA), 1930s-1957 (Box 31, Folder 65)
    - Ennis, Seamus, undated (Box 31, Folder 66)
    - Erin's Pride Orchestra feat. Tommy Caulfield (Phila, PA), 1930s-1940s (Box 31, Folder 67)
    - Farrell, Laura and Jim, undated (Box 31, Folder 68)
    - Feis, undated (Box 34, Folder 23, Box 31, Folder 69)
    - Festival of American Folklife, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 25, Box 31, Folder 70)
    - Festival of American Folklife, Feb, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 71, Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Festival of American Folklife, undated (Box 31, Folder 72)
    - Festival of Mountain Music and Dance, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 73)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 26, Box 31, Folder 74)
    - Festivals: Glen Echo, Jan, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 75, Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Festivals: Irish Vendors, undated (Box 31, Folder 76, Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Festivals: Irish Vendors, undated (Box 31, Folder 77, Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Festivals: Various Artists: Reavy, Caulfield, Carroll, Reynolds, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 78)
    - Festivals: Various Artists, Aug, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 79)
    - Festivals: Various Artists, undated (Box 31, Folder 80)
    - Fitzgerald, Bridget, undated (Box 31, Folder 81)
    - Fitzpatrick, Mike and Maureen, undated (Box 31, Folder 82)
    - Flanagan, Mike, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 83)
    - Flatley, Michael, 1970s (Box 34, Folder 29, Box 31, Folder 84)
    - Flying Cloud, undated (Box 31, Folder 85)
    - Golden, Donnie and Eileen, undated (Box 34, Folder 30, Box 31, Folder 86)
    - Green Fields of America, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 31, Box 31, Folder 87)
    - Green Fields of America, undated (Box 31, Folder 88)
    - Green Fields of America, undated (Box 31, Folder 89)
    - Green Fields of America: New York Harbor Festival, 1986 (Box 34, Folder 32, Box 31, Folder 90)
    - Green Fields of America: New York Harbor Festival, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 91)
    - Green Fields of America: New York Harbor Festival, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 92)
    - Green Fields of America: Milwaukee Irish Fest, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 93)
    - Green Grass Cloggers, undated (Box 31, Folder 94)
    - Arthur Hall Dance Ensemble, undated (Box 31, Folder 95)
    - Harpists, 1980s (Box 31, Folder 96)
    - Hart, Tony, undated (Box 31, Folder 97)
    - Harte, Frank, 1996, undated (Box 31, Folder 98)
    - Hickey, Mick: Bermuda, undated (Box 31, Folder 99, Box 34, Folder 33)
    - International House: Ethnic Folklife Festival, undated (Box 31, Folder 100)
    - International House: FAIS, undated (Box 31, Folder 101)
    - International Village Fair, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 102)
    - International Village Fair: Contact Sheets (Celtic Performers), 1987 (Box 31, Folder 103, Box 34, Folder 34)
    - International Village Fair: Contact Sheets, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 35-49, Box 31, Folder 104)
    - International Village Fair: Contact Sheets, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 35-49, Box 31, Folder 105)
    - International Village Fair: Contact Sheets, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 35-49, Box 31, Folder 106)
    - International Village Fair: Contact Sheets, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 35-49, Box 31, Folder 107)
    - International Village Fair: Contact Sheets, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 35-49, Box 31, Folder 108)
    - International Village Fair: Contact Sheets, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 35-49, Box 31, Folder 109)
    - International Village Fair: Contact Sheets, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 110, Box 34, Folder 35-49)
    - Irish Musicians of America: Local 17 (Phila, PA), 1930s (Box 31, Folder 111)
    - Irish Tradition, undated (Box 31, Folder 112)
    - Ivers, Eileen, undated (Box 31, Folder 113)
    - Jackson, John and Peter, undated (Box 31, Folder 114)
    - Japanese Dancers, undated (Box 31, Folder 115)
    - Johnstons, undated (Box 31, Folder 116)
    - Johnstons (Oversized), undated (Box Shared Tamiment 065, Folder 14)
    - Keane, James, undated (Box 31, Folder 117)
    - Keane, Jimmy, undated (Box 31, Folder 118)
    - Keane, Kathleen, undated (Box 31, Folder 119)
    - Keegan Kevin, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 50, Box 31, Folder 120)
    - Kelly, John and John Vesey, undated (Box 31, Folder 121)
    - Kennedy, Ian, undated (Box 31, Folder 122)
    - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald, undated (Box 31, Folder 123)
    - Lyn, Dana, undated (Box 31, Folder 124)
    - MacIsaac, Dave, undated (Box 31, Folder 125)
    - MacMathuna, Ciaran, undated (Box 31, Folder 126)
    - Macon, "Uncle" Dave, undated (Box 31, Folder 127)
    - MacQueen, Maybelle Chisolm, undated (Box 31, Folder 128)
    - McBee, Hamper, May, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 129)
    - McComiskey, Billy: Wedding, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 130, Box 34, Folder 51)
    - McDermott's Handy, undated (Box 31, Folder 131)
    - McGettigan's Irish Minstrels (Phil, PA), undated (Box 31, Folder 132)
    - McGinley, Danny, undated (Box 31, Folder 133)
    - McGlynn, Sean, undated (Box 31, Folder 134)
    - McGlynn, Sean and Jack Coen, undated (Box 31, Folder 135)
    - McKenna, Joe and Antoinette, undated (Box 31, Folder 136)
    - McKenna, Joe and Antoinette, undated (Box 31, Folder 137)
    - McMahon, Tony, undated (Box 31, Folder 138)
    - McNulty Family, 1950s (Box 31, Folder 139)
    - Milwaukee Irish Festival, Feb, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Milwaukee Irish Festival, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Milwaukee Irish Festival, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Milwaukee Irish Festival, undated (Box 34, Folder 53, Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Mollys, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Moloney, Mick, 1983-2000 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Moloney, Mick, undated (Box 34, Folder 54, Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Moloney, Mick, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Moloney, Mick, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Moloney, Mick, undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Moloney, Mick (Oversized), 1992-1995, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 065, Folder 12)
    - Moloney, Mick: Family, undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Moloney, Mick: Graduation, May, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Moloney, Mick and Liz Carroll, undated (Box 32, Folder 13, Box 34, Folder 55)
    - Moloney, Mick, Seamus Egan, Eileen Ivers and Jimmy Keane, undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Moloney, Mick, Seamus Egan, Eileen Ivers, Jimmy Keane and Tommy Sands, undated (Box 32, Flat-file 15)
    - Moloney, Mick, Eileen Ivers and Tommy Sands, undated (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Moloney, Mick, Zan McLeod, Kieran O'Hare and Kathleen Keane, undated (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Moloney, Mick and Brendan Mulvihill, undated (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Moloney, Mick, Martin Mulvihill and Eugene O'Donnell, undated (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Moloney, Mick and Robbie O'Connell, undated (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Moloney, Mick, Robbie O'Connell and James Keane, undated (Box 34, Folder 59, Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Moloney, Mick, Robbie O'Connell and Jimmy Keane, undated (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Moloney, Mick, Robbie O'Connell and Jimmy Keane, undated (Box 34, Folder 59, Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Moloney, Mick, Robbie O'Connell, Jimmy Keane, Eileen Ivers and Seamus Egan, undated (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Moloney, Mick, Robbie O'Connell, Kimmy Keane and Regan Wick, undated (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Moloney, Mick, Robbie O'Connell, Jimmy Keane and Liz Carroll, undated (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell, undated (Box 34, Folder 60, Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell, undated (Box 34, Folder 61, Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell, undated (Box 32, Folder 29, Box 34, Folder 62)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell, undated (Box 32, Folder 30, Box 34, Folder 63)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell, undated (Box 32, Folder 31, Box 34, Folder 64)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell, undated (Box 32, Folder 32, Box 34, Folder 65)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell, undated (Box 32, Folder 33, Box 34, Folder 66)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell, undated (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell, undated (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Moloney, Mick and Eugene O'Donnell (Oversized), undated (Box Shared Tamiment 065, Folder 11)
    - Moloney, Mick, Eugene O'Donnell and Seamus Egan, Aug, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 36, Box 34, Folder 67)
    - Moloney, Mick, Eugene O'Donnell and Seamus Egan, undated (Box 32, Folder 37, Box 34, Folder 68)
    - Moloney, Mick, Eugene O'Donnell and Seamus Egan, undated (Box 32, Folder 38, Box 34, Folder 69)
    - Moloney, Mick, Eugene O'Donnell and Seamus Egan, undated (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Moloney, Mick, Eugene O'Donnell and Seamus Egan (Oversized), undated (Box Shared Tamiment 142, Folder 1)
    - Moloney, Mick, Eugene O'Donnell and Tommy Sands, undated (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Moloney, Mick and Old Time Musicians, undated (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Moloney, Mick, Tommy Sands, Seamus Egan and Winifred Horan, undated (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Moloney, Mick, Tommy Sands and Eileen Ivers, undated (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Moloney, Phil, undated (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Molsky, Bruce, undated (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Montserrat, Feb, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Mulcahy Family, 1990s (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - Mulhaire, Martin, Nov 20, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - Mulvihill, Brendan, 1982, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - NEA - Knoxville Documentation Project, c.1980 (Box 32, Folder 50, Box 34, Folder 73)
    - NEA - Knoxville Documentation Project, c.1980 (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - Northeast WInds, undated (Box 32, Folder 52)
    - North Texas Irish Festival, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 53)
    - Ochs, Bill, undated (Box 32, Folder 54)
    - O'Connell, Robbie, 1980s (Box 32, Folder 55)
    - O'Connor, Gerry, undated (Box 32, Folder 56)
    - O'Connor, Mairtin, undated (Box 32, Folder 57)
    - O'Donnell, Eugene, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 58)
    - O'Donnell, Eugene, undated (Box 32, Folder 59)
    - O'Hare, Kieran, undated (Box 32, Folder 60)
    - O'Kane Family, undated (Box 32, Folder 61)
    - Old Time Musicians, undated (Box 32, Folder 62)
    - O'Sullivan, Jerry, undated (Box 32, Folder 63)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 64)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 65)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 66)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 67)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 68)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 69)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 70)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 71)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, 1997 (Box 32, Folder 72)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 73)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 74)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 75)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 76)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 77)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 78, Box 34, Folder 76)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 79, Box 34, Folder 77)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 80, Box 34, Folder 78)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 81, Box 34, Folder 79)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 82, Box 34, Folder 80)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 83, Box 34, Folder 81)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 84, Box 34, Folder 82)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 34, Folder 83, Box 32, Folder 85)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 34, Folder 84, Box 32, Folder 86)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 34, Folder 85, Box 32, Folder 87)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 88)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 89)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 90)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 91)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 92)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 93)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 94)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 95)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 96)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 97)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 32, Folder 98)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Package Tours: Ireland, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Panoramas, 1990-1992 (Flat-file-folder 5, Tray 2)
    - Patterson, Johnny, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival, 1978, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Pleneros, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Port Penn Interpretive Center, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Posen, Shelley, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Rafferty, Mike and Mary, undated (Box 34, Folder 88, Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Ramblers (Phila, PA), 1940s (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Reavy, Ed, undated (Box 34, Folder 89, Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Reavy, Ed, undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Reilly, Marie, undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Reiniga, Pete, undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Robinson, LaVaughn, 1980s (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Roche, undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Russell, Micho, undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Saint Malachy's, Aug, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 19, Box 34, Folder 90)
    - Sands, Colum and Tommy, undated (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Sessions at Moloney's, undated (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Sessions feat. McGlynn, Carroll, Coens, undated (Box 33, Folder 22, Box 34, Folder 91)
    - Sessions feat. McGlynn, Carroll, Coens (Box 33, Folder 23, Box 34, Folder 91)
    - Sessions feat. McGlynn, Carroll, Coens (Box 34, Folder 91, Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Shannon, Joe and Johnny McGreevy, 1970s (Box 34, Folder 92, Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Shute, Bill and Lisa, undated (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Smithsonian Festival of American Folklife, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 27, Box 34, Folder 93)
    - Smithsonian Festival of American Folklife, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Smithsonian Festival of American Folklife (Oversized), 1976 (Box Shared Tamiment 065, Folder 13)
    - Sproule, Daithi, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Dan Sullivan's Shamrock Band (Boston, MA), undated (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Sweeney's Men, undated (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Tannahill Weavers, undated (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Tap Dancers, undated (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Taylor, Sandra, undated (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Tennessee Banjo Institute, Cedars of Lebanon, November 1-3, 1990 (panoramic group portrait) (Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file 2)
    - Toner, Michael P., undated (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Tory Island feat. P.J.Hernon, undated (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Touchstone, undated (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Tunney, Paddy, undated (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 33, Folder 39, Box 34, Folder 94)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Van Kleeck, Dick, undated (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Vesey, John, undated (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Watson, Jim (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - White House Performance, undated (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Wick, Regan and Linnane, undated (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Williams, John, undated (Box 33, Folder 47)
    - Winch, Jesse and Terry, undated (Box 33, Folder 48)
    - Wolf Trap, undated (Box 34, Folder 97, Box 33, Folder 49)
    - World's Fair of 1982 (Knoxville, Tenn) (Box 34, Folder 98, Box 33, Folder 50)
    - World's Fair of 1982 (Knoxville, Tenn) (Box 33, Folder 51)
    - World's Fair of 1982 (Knoxville, Tenn), undated (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - Subseries C: Negatives
    - Augusta Heritage Center (Elkins, W. Va.), undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Byrne, Tom and Tom McCaffrey, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 20, Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Cahill, Eddie, undated (Box 31, Folder 22, Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Carroll, Liz, undated (Box 34, Folder 4, Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Carton, Mickey, Mary Carton and Ruthie Morrissey, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 5, Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Catskills Festival (Leeds, NY), 1978 (Box 31, Folder 27, Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Caulfield, Thomas, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Cherish the Ladies, undated (Box 34, Folder 8, Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Chicago Musicians: Keanes, Shannon, Cooley, undated (Box 31, Folder 32, Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Chicago Musicians: Rice, etc., undated (Box 31, Folder 33, Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Clancy Brothers with Tommy Makem, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Coen, Fr. Charlie, 1979 (Box 31, Folder 38, Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Coen, Fr. Charlie, undated (Box 34, Folder 13, Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Coen, Jack, undated (Box 31, Folder 41, Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Comhaltas on Tour (Chicago, IL): Shannon, McGlynn,Coens, Henry, Flatley, late 1970s (Box 31, Folder 42, Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Comhaltas on Tour (Chicago, IL): Shannon, McGlynn,Coens, Henry, Flatley, late 1970s (Box 31, Folder 43, Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Comhaltas Convention, undated (Box 31, Folder 46, Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Concert for Joe Doherty: Symphony Space (New York, NY), 1990 (Box 31, Folder 48, Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Concert for Joe Doherty: Symphony Space (New York, NY), 1990 (Box 34, Folder 19, Box 31, Folder 48)
    - Cruise, Mar, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Cruise: Virgin Islands, undated (Box 34, Folder 21, Box 31, Folder 55)
    - Cruise: Virgin Islands, undated (Box 31, Folder 56, Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Feis, undated (Box 31, Folder 69, Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Festival of American Folklife, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 24, Box 31, Folder 70)
    - Festival of American Folklife, Feb, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 71, Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Festival of Traditional American Dance, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 26, Box 31, Folder 74)
    - Festivals: Glen Echo, Jan, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 27, Box 31, Folder 75)
    - Festivals: Irish Vendors, undated (Box 34, Folder 28, Box 31, Folder 77, Folder 76)
    - Flatley, Michael, 1970s (Box 34, Folder 29, Box 31, Folder 84)
    - Golden, Donnie and Eileen, undated (Box 31, Folder 86, Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Green Fields of America, undated (Box 31, Folder 87, Box 34, Folder 31)
    - Green Fields of America: New York Harbor Festival, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 89, Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Hickey, Mick: Bermuda, undated (Box 31, Folder 99, Box 34, Folder 33)
    - International Village Fair (Celtic Performers), 1987 (Box 31, Folder 103, Box 34, Folder 34)
    - International Village Fair, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 104-110, Box 34, Folder 35)
    - International Village Fair, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 104-110, Box 34, Folder 36)